ABOUT

I am a UI/UX Designer and Front-End Web Developer who makes visualizations come to life. I strive to make beautiful user-friendly interfaces based on research and data. Besides design, I also enjoy interacting directly with clients, and as a result, have a passion for learning foreign languages.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

React, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, SASS, LESS, Gulp, Github, Git, Web Accessibility, Email coding, MailChimp

DESIGN

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, InVision, Sketch, Acrylic Painting, Illustrations, Photography

LANGUAGE

Japanese Language Proficiency Test (N1- Advanced) 2014 - Fluent in Japanese

Test of Chinese as a Foreign Language (Level 3) 2013 - Proficient in Mandarin

Conversant in Spanish

AWARDS

2017 (July) - Always Hungry Award

Awarded at Hungry Catering for building the company's new website from the ground up and always working efficiently to produce excellent work.

2013 - Huayu Enrichment Scholarship

Awarded \$9,840 from the Taiwan Ministry of Education to study Mandarin in Taiwan



maureenvogel@outlook.com

github.com/maureenv/

in linkedin.com/in/maureenvogel/

MAUREEN VOGEL

DEVELOPER | UI/UX DESIGNER

WORK EXPERIENCE

ASSOCIATE PRODUCT MANAGER

HUNGRY CATERING

Arlington, VA, April 2019 ~ Present

Create product prototypes using Sketch/Photoshop and InVision. Conduct UI/UX research for new products and features. Monitor company's e-commerce website's Google Analytics data to improve conversion rates. Work with company's founder and CEO to prioritize features on the product roadmap.

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER | UI/UX DESIGNER

HUNGRY CATERING

Arlington, VA, July 2017 ~ April 2019

Code responsive application interfaces from the ground up in React.js and CSS/Sass from Photoshop mocks. Use Browserstack.com to test and fix cross-browser issues. Code marketing emails using MailChimp. Improve the website's user interface and experience through client feedback. The website I built can be viewed at https://tryhungry.com/.

JUNIOR FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

SYMPLICITY CORPORATION

Arlington, VA, July 2016 ~ July 2017

Maintained and updated software's user interface using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery. Updated code to be ARIA/WCAG 2.0 compliant for web accessibility. Fixed cross-browser issues in IE10 +, Edge, Firefox, Chrome, and Safari. Created features from mocks provided by the UI/UX team. Assisted quality assurance testers during testing to troubleshoot issues.

ART DIRECTOR

A2L CONSULTING

Alexandria, VA, Apr. 2015 ~ Dec. 2015

Advised lawyers on how to communicate their message through visual design. Created persuasive graphics using Photoshop and PowerPoint to present in court. Designed marketing, sales and promotional material using Photoshop & Illustrator.

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE COURSE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Washington D.C., Feb. 2016 ~ Apr. 2016

Studied Web Development in a Full-Stack Web Development Immersive Course. Designed and developed web applications using JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, jQuery, HTML5, and CSS.

B.A. INTERNATIONAL STUDIES

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, IRVINE

Irvine, CA, Sep. 2012 ~ Sep. 2013

Studied International Relations with a focus on Asia.